Guide to the Keith-McHenry-Pond Family Papers, 1841-1961
The Bancroft Library.
- Worcester, Joseph, 1836-1913 See also: Herrin, William Franklin Porter, Bruce Scott, Irving Murray Worcester, Alfred Worcester, Benjamin
  - 18 letters, 1890-1911 and n.d., to William Keith. With these: notes re Keith by Worcester - in E. K. Pond's handwriting. (Box 3)
  - 3 letters, 1911-1913, to Mary (McHenry) Keith. Mainly re William Keith's estate. (Box 13)
  - 2 letters, 1892 and n.d., to Emily Parsons Babcock Hay. (Box 21)
  - Letter, June 15, 1884, to Charles William Keith. In Miscellaneous Correspondence (Carton 9)